It's my life.
It's your life.
Fighting for tomorrow.
Go get what you really want.
I want more. Any one more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life. It's your life.
Run like a wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your call.
Let's keep on going on the stage.
Let's do it again, you
know what I mean, baby.
No one can make my dream come true!
Don't you feel it?
I really don't know what is
Something is testing me every day.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
I know I never wanna come back here.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away the great
end of the unknown rules.
Standing up, blowing up.
My dream is getting wilder.
I'm not afraid, beat me, hit me.
I will never turn around.
Another day, another chance.
You know it's never too late.
If I can do it, so can you only without.
It's my life, it's your life.
Party for tomorrow, go
get what you really want.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the door.
It's my life, it's your life.
Run like a wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going, roaring.
It's my life, it's your life.
Fighting for your eyes that
I want, but your weary ones.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the gate.
It's my life, it's your life,
shine like a star to be good.
I know you're strong, just that
you can't achieve your best.
Let's keep on going out of day.
You make my day every day.
Stop it, Bellamy! Shut up!
I've heard enough from you!
Let me settle this on
my own terms, damn it!
This fight is tough!
We shouldn't have to do this!
Who cares?
You can just stand there
if you don't accept it.
But I'm fighting you.
Either way.
I'll show you what I'm made of.
My conviction is.
Nothing to scum man, damn it!
Damn it!
I thought I was going to die.
There he is!
Mortica!
This guy's hard-headed
in more ways than one.
So what if you know how my power works?
That doesn't mean you can
beat me, or even catch me!
Don't congratulate yourself so quickly!
Come back!
Take him down!
Don't move, Pirate Hunter!
This is the end of the road for you!
This is a massive pain in the ass!
Commodore Dignity!
Now I turn hard!
Please, sir, no!
Have mercy on me! No!
Wait, why are we lining up anyway?
Killer Foley!
Nice one, pal.
Forge on ahead. Thanks.
You're from the Coliseum, right?
That's right.
My name is Orlumbus.
If this battle were at sea,
I would have rained terror upon my foes
with the full force of my Aunt Maria fleet.
But seeing as I'm shorthanded, I'll
have to leave that stone monster to you.
No problem.
Now, where did that
giant bastard run off to?
Well, there's my answer.
Lord Pika took over the whole plateau!
Let's see if you can dodge my...
There's no way that's your real laugh!
What?
I don't get it.
Is there something funny about my laugh?
It sounds way too stupid to be real!
You're the stupid one to say that!
You know what happens
when Lord Pika gets angry?
Ah! Ow!
Ah!
Ha!
Wanna get big? Fine.
When I cut you down, it's
gonna feel real good.
Watch it Pika you've
got friends down here.
You're about to squash destruction cannon
Ignore me at your own barrel kid.
Why are you beating around the bush
so much because I'm your enemy I?
Don't care, be honest with me.
I don't know what you're
talking about, lady.
Don't play dumb.
This next blow will strike
straight through your heart.
You said that you were
aiming for my heart.
I'll hold this hand till you die.
You wanted to hold hands our whole life.
Don't want to lose you on this one.
And you never want to lose me, right?
If your feelings for me
really are that strong,
then I don't care if we're enemies or not.
Oh, I understand.
You need me, don't you?
Lord Vice shows no mercy, huh?
Even a mighty warrior of Elbop
gets crushed under his weight.
Okay, let's get a better look at the yinz.
Hirudin is down, so let's start
searching for my next target.
Ooh, that's Roro Noa Zoro.
You're in our way, you giant roadblock.
My dream was to become the strongest.
The king of all the giants.
But look at me now.
I lost in the competition.
I was transformed into a toy.
I was saved, but I
failed to repay my debt.
This is pathetic.
I vowed to aid the Strahats, even
if it cost me my life itself.
And yet here I lie, defeated,
but shamelessly still alive.
He he he, Ton Ton!
Was my gratitude truly so shallow?
Here I come, Lorenoa!
Oh, that's that good.
Destructive, one thousand ton fights!
No!
My honor will not allow it!
He got up
Forgive me But if you would
Please let me handle him
I root you
Still stand here And right
after I gave you such a
proper pound Then I'll make
it even heavier for you
Hellish 10 ,000 ton five
I really hope there are still some
bones left over for Kurasheen.
I'm no use to my allies, dear.
But as long as I can move even a single
arm, I can defeat an enemy leader.
The last of my life, I
place in this first...
GANAKA!
It stops struggling.
This is way too heavy.
Get squashed! High Routine!
Let him fly to the kingdom of the gods!
Orp eyes!
The birdcage! No!
He's not slowing down at all!
Orp night, stop!
You're gonna get shredded!
Those skies are still too far for you.
You're no bird after all.
Lord, fight!
Enjoy your nap and when you
wake up the cage will be gone
Your aim sure sucks.
It got away.
You're just a one-trick pony.
Gotta figure something out.
Need some assistance, pirate hunter?
The punching guy.
The name is Elisabello.
King Riku's an old friend.
I hope to restore him to power.
I'm charged and ready.
I can unleash my king punch once per hour.
Have you figured out how that
stone giant's ability works?
Yeah, a long time ago.
Then tell me and I'll finish him off.
Sorry, pal, but I want to beat him myself.
Hold on to that trump card of yours.
We still don't know what's to come.
Then I'll take your
advice and lead us to you.
You big stupid rock.
Whatever you're plotting, it won't work.
I see his secret technique!
The deadly bat princess!
Not done yet!
Prepare to die!
Geofist!
Ice cream gel!
Wow!
I see stiff shoulder!
Immortal Warrior Junk Pain.
That's the true power of old age.
Xin Zhao's bounty is huge,
but he's just not old enough.
No one understands the meaning
of pain better than the elderly.
That is the greatness of
Geo-Fist, with a capital G!
I thoroughly oppose it. Who?
Your engagement.
Who are you even talking to?
What are you talking about, old man?
There's no engagement!
You're not marrying me?
Why is that so shocking to you?
We're fighting!
Sigh, you're already
arranged to marry Euclesia,
the daughter of the
Nihushmi army's leader.
High five!
I know that!
Frankly, I don't give a damn who I marry!
You make whatever political
alliance you want!
I don't care about romance,
so it's all the same to me!
You've done it now!
Only a fool would dare to ignore Lao Chi!
To be so angry!
Huh?
He didn't hear a word they said!
Wait a second, he is angry.
Look, there's an aura of
rage tipping off of his head.
That's his soul!
Guess he reached the
natural end of his life.
Yeah, okay, but kind of
awkward timing, isn't it?
No, it can't be!
Lao-G, stay with us!
We need you!
Please come back! Black? Black?
Huh?
He couldn't understand what we
said, but he came back anyway.
Oh, thank goodness.
Oh, ooh.
I see the rigors of age
have not been kind to you.
Look who's talking!
I've had enough, Si!
Change-out's got family drama! Huh?
He couldn't hear anyway!
Let's discuss this another time, okay?
Your collar was crooked.
There. Dammit!
You're not my wife! Stop that!
Stay away from me, you freak!
What is your endgame?
Are you trying to seduce me?
We're supposed to be
fighting, not getting married!
Why would I fight you when you need me?
Let me be useful.
Tell me what I can do.
Oh, really?
You want to help me?
Then why don't you die?
If I let you walk away from this,
and you cause trouble for
Straw Hat and his friends,
then my debt will never be repaid.
We're laying our lives down
to defeat you executives.
That's the least we can do.
So fight me or die!
No problem.
Then I'll die happily.
I don't mind at all if it'll help you.
Uh, wait!
I love helping people more
than anything in the world.
I'm glad you need me.
Cut that out! I was kidding!
Just trash-talking my enemy!
I can't let her battle conclude this way!
I'd regret it for the rest of my life!
What are you doing, Psy?
Your enemy wants to kill
herself, doesn't she?
Let her!
Just who are you fighting for anyway?
What?
As a leader of our army, you
can't afford to show mercy!
Shut up, old man!
You're not my master anymore, so cram it!
Hey, stop!
To be useful, even in death.
This is all that I've ever wanted.
Why did you have a child?
She won't contribute a damned thing,
but she'll eat plenty, I'm sure.
We have too many mouths to feed.
Take her to the mountain
and leave her there.
Mommy, where are we going?
Mommy, don't leave me here, please! No!
No, Mommy, take me with me!
This place is scary!
I'm leaving you because you're useless.
You're not wanted or needed, okay?
Not by this world, and
not by anyone in it.
Even you?
Even you don't need me, Mommy.
You were wrong, Mother.
Now someone does need me.
I said stop, you stupid broad!
You're the one who's stupid!
What the...
He's a monster!
Look up there!
Damn you, Sai!
You're a disgrace to the Hapasui army!
Either correct your actions or
resign from your post immediately.
This is my problem.
So stay out of it, old man.
Like hell I will.
I sure can't check it.
This is scary.
His headbutt can split a glacier in half.
I'll set you straight with my drill head.
And that goes for the both of you.
Drill Drago.
Who shall get healed?
I finally found my place.
This is all I could ask for.
You need to value your
life more than that!
I don't understand.
Why did you stop me?
Let me die!
Isn't that the only way I can help you?
If I die, I can finally be
useful to someone, can't I?
Poor girl.
The world you live in is twisted.
They taught you all wrong.
Don Chin-Jow's famous drill
head is bent sideways!
I can't believe I did that!
My attack was that powerful?
You're surprised.
You're not the one whose head
is bent at a 90 degree angle.
They're gonna fight to
the death, aren't they?
Your power has awakened
and your form is true.
Though your training
was filled with blood,
sweat and tears, it
has indeed borne fruit.
Grabs, I...
I'm so proud of you.
The Hoshokan technique has
finally found its true heir.
Sai, your kick shall inherit the title
Drill Dragon Nail as my head did before it.
Having witnessed its strength,
I may rest easy, knowing that you
can split the Continent of Ice.
The Hapa Sui army is yours.
Truly and completely now, I shall
cancel your arranged marriage.
Your life is yours to live as you please.
To be frank, my chronic pain has been
acting up since the battle with Straw Hat,
and I haven't been able to
fight to my true potential.
I'm no spring chicken.
I had started to worry,
but now I know my legacy.
YAAAHHHHH!
Ohhhh!
Behold, the Seal of Chi!
Ta-da-da!
Ahhhh!
Graf! No!
A perfect Chi!
Mh!
He took down Don Chin-Jow with one shot!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ah!
Geo-fist, ultimate technique,
battle insurance fist!
A safety precaution to
counteract infirmary or old age.
By performing Ji Gong exercises,
you can store away muscle from
your prime to draw upon later.
Now I have combined the experience
of age with the vitality of youth!
No one can stand before me!
My power is sublime!
What business does a filthy
monkey from Kano have with me?
And pay back the debt of
honor I owe to Straw Hat.
What a foolish ape.
Straw Hat will not
defeat the young master.
Your honor is meaningless.
We'll see. Ha-da!
Listen, this kingdom
belongs to the young master.
Therefore, all those who set foot
here are no more than his slaves.
Your faith in Straw Hat
has ensured your death.
I will triumph!
And the young master's birth
cave will be your grave!
Grave with a capital G!
Huh?
You're a quick little
monkey, I'll grant you that.
However, Baby Five is ours.
You won't...
Take her away!
Aw, that's so sweet!
You wait right there, Baby Five.
I'll protect you and pound this interloper
into the ground with a capital G!
Oh, what should I do?
I can't believe they're fighting over me!
Careful! Stay back!
You're every bit as green as I thought.
If you had any sense,
you would have used Baby Five as
a shield to gain the upper hand.
Do you even realize
what Baby Five is worth?
She'd give her life in an
instant if one of us needed it.
Why, there's scarcely a more useful
woman in the world, one might say.
Useful?
I'll send you to hell with
my final secret technique!
How about this?
We'll fight for Baby Five.
And once I win, then I'm
gonna take her as my wife!
Whoa!
Drill Dragon, kneel!
Now say goodbye!
Jeez!
You cursed gorilla.
Gorilla with a capital G!
Call me the dog!
Another battle on the second level
of the plateau comes to an end,
with two executives defeated.
Lao-G fell.
Baby-Five fell.
In love.